Life tries to break you. Love holds you together.
Not Easily Broken is a drama, romance film directed by Bill Duke.
A car accident and shifting affections test the bond between a married couple.
Dave Johnson, played by Morris Chestnut.
Clarice Clark, played by Taraji P. Henson.
Julie Sawyer, played by Maeve Quinlan.
Tree, played by Kevin Hart.
Mary 'Mama' Clark, played by Jenifer Lewis.
Brock Houseman, played by Eddie Cibrian.
Not Easily Broken is a 2009 American romantic
comedy-drama film directed by Bill Duke.
The film is written by Brian Bird based on T.
Jakes' 2006 novel of the same name.
It stars Taraji P.
Henson and Morris Chestnut.
The tone is emotional.